Finding Aid for Walter Jarocki Photographs, 1937, 1948, 1952-1959, 1970s-early 1980s
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- "Gordie," 1970s-1980s
  - St. Ladislaus basketball game March 1971 (Box 3)
  - Untitled Envelope 1
    - Couples seating outside, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Demolition site, 5 negatives (Box 3)
    - Hamtramck's anniversary (Box 3)
    - Knights of Columbus ceremony, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Kowalski sausage (Mayor Kozaren), 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Mayor Robert Kozaren's office (Box 3)
    - Mayor Robert Kozaren with unidentified (Box 3)
    - Office workers, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Young people taking notes (Box 3)
  - Untitled Envelope 2
    - Hamtramck Chancellors football game, 11 negatives (Box 3)
    - School children, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Unidentified girl, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Woods, 2 negatives (Box 3)
  - Untitled Envelope 3
    - Bank of Commerce open house (Box 3)
    - Car accident on freeway, 4 negatives (Box 3)
    - Christmas, 3 negatives (Box 3)
    - Planting a tree, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Shifrin Willens Jewelers, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - St. Ladislaus basketball game, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Storefronts, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Unidentified, 3 negatives (Box 3)
    - Unidentified group (Box 3)
  - Untitled Envelope 4
    - Group portraits, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Individual portraits, 3 negatives (Box 3)
    - License plates, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Snow shoveling, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Street views, 5 negatives (Box 3)
    - Wedding, 4 negatives (Box 3)
- Unknown photographer 1970s-1980s
  The Unknown Photographer series (approximately 70 photonegatives; 1970s-1980s) contains one original envelope bearing crossed out names "Gordie" and "Mitch," containing photonegatives with images similar to those in the "Gordie" series: school children, athletic events, street views, mayor Kozaren, portraits, etc. Also included in this series are photonegatives that were found loose in the collection: group photos, street scenes, athletic teams and events, etc.
  - Untitled envelope
    - Disrepairs, interior, 3 negatives (Box 3)
    - Hamtramck Chancellors football game, 5 negatives (Box 3)
    - Hamtramck police car, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Immaculate Conception football team, 4 negatives (Box 3)
    - Mayor Robert Kozaren and others, 2 negatives (Box 3)
    - Office scenes, 6 negatives (Box 3)
    - School children, 14 negatives (Box 3)
    - St. Ladislaus basketball game, 4 negatives (Box 3)
    - Store interior (Box 3)
    - Street view (Box 3)
  - Undated loose photographs
    - Bicyclists (Box 3)
    - Classrooms (Box 3)
    - Exterior of building (Box 3)
    - Group photo July 9 1972 (Box 3)
    - Hamtramck Chancellors (Box 3)
    - Hamtramck's 50th anniversary (1972 ?) (Box 3)
    - Landscaping (Box 3)
    - Parked cars (Box 3)
    - St. Ladislaus baseball game (Box 3)
    - Unidentified man (Box 3)